Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Public Programs to Create Jobs, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. Bibliography; Selected References No. 125. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Public Employment Policies and Priorities, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    By National Manpower Policy Task Force. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Research Report Number Three: National Job Availability, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    By Manpower Research Council. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: America's Need: One Million Jobs Now, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    By George Meany. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Manpower Forecasting Through the Occupational Needs Survey, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    By Rutgers University, Institute of Management and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Negotiating Annual Wage, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By Waldo E. Fisher. Speech given at the AMA Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Preparing a Guaranteed Employment Plan That Fits UAW Members Like a Glove, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By UAW-CIO Education Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Questions and Answers About the UAW-CIO Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By Bureau of National Affairs, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Economic Safeguards in UAW-CIO Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By Industrial Relations Research Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Questions and Answers about the UAW-CIO Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By Bureau of National Affairs, Inc. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Fact Sheet: Procter & Gamble's Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By Procter & Gamble. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Guaranteed Employment in 1955!, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By CIO Department of Education and Research. Pamphlet No. 272 from April, 1955 "Economic Outlook". Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet: Procter & Gamble's Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By Procter & Gamble. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Guaranteed Employment and Wage Plans, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    By William A. Berridge; Cedric Wolfe. No. 428 in the series "National Economic Problems". Item is in English.
  - Item 10: UAW-CIO Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Use of Research in Employment Stabilization, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Annual Wage and Guaranteed-Employment Plans in Union Agreements, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Can Government Guarantee Full Employment?, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
    By Emerson P. Schmidt. Post-War Readjustments Bulletin No. 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employment Regularization, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Preliminary Report on Study of Regularization of Employment and Improvement of Labor Conditions in the Automobile Industry: Appendix A, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Problem of Full Employment: An Outline for Study Circles, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    By Joan Robinson. W.E.A. Study Outlines No. 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Economics of Full Employment: An Analysis of the U.N. Report on National and International Measures for Full Employment, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    By Wilhelm Ropke. "National Economic Problems" No. 444. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Federal Tax Program to Promote Full Employment, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    By CIO, Department of Education and Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: From War to Work: How to Get Full Employment and Keep It Going, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    By Survey Graphic. Vol. XXXII, No. 5; Eighth in "Calling America" Series. Item is in English.
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Full Employment Act of 1945, Publication (Box 8, Folder 25)
    By Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce. The Economic Sentinel Vol. 3, No. 3; Correspondence from Harold W. Wright (Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce) inside. Item is in English.
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Role of the Employment Service, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Bibliography. Item is in English.
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Key Policies for Full Employment, Publication (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Local Emmployer's Associations, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    By William H. Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employer-Employee Relations Activites of Trade Associations, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Box 8, Folder (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Present System of Trade and Payments vs. Full Employment and Welfare State, Publication (Box 8, Folder 29)
    By Eprimes Eshag. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employment - 96% Full or 4% Empty?, Publication (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: It's showdown Time for Featherbedding on the Railroads, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Alfred Steinberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Dead Horse and the Featherbird, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Paul Jacobs. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Menace of Restrictive Work Practices, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Why Railroad Featherbeds Must Go!, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Railway Digest. Railway Digest Vol. 14, No. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Anti-Productivity: Management's Dilemma, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By James W. Oram. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Let's Make Way for Progress The Case Against State 'Full Crew' Railroad Laws, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Transportation Association of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Featherbedding Hurts Everybody!, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Association of American Railroads. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Excess-Crew Laws: Featherbedding by Legislation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Association of American Railroads. November 4, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Surplus Diesel Fireman Position, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: "Featherbedding" - A List of References Arranged Chronologically - with Index of Authors 1938-1958, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Featherbedding: Pitfall on the Path of Progress, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By J. Handly Wright. Address before the Southern and Southwestern Railway Club on July 17, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: How Workers Evaluate Issues in Crucial Rail Dispute, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By The Forum. The Forum Vol. 63, No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Case for Locomative Helpers (Firemen), Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Dick Murway; Bill Loftus. Press Release on October 18, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Are Railroad Workers 'Featherbedding'?, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Eli Oliver. Address before the Industrial Relations Research Association on May 27, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Labor Vol. XLL, No. 16, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Labor. Newspaper; November 14, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Featherbedding: Crisis Issue in collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By Arnold R. Deutsch. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Press Release: January 17, 1969, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    By National Railway Labor Conference. Background information attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Featherbedding and Technological Change in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    By James D. Boydston. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: More Fireman Featherbedding?, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    By National Railway Labor Conference. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Chamber Sponsorship of Foremen's Clubs and Personnel Executives' Clubs, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Training of Supervisors, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    By Ministry of Labour and National Service. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Techniques of Successful Foremanship, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    By Eugene E. Jennings. Wisconsin Commerce Reports Vol. 1, No. 4. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Training of Superviersors, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    By Anglo-American Council on Productivity. Report of a visit to the U.S.A. in 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Strengthening Management Teamwork, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Guide for Foreman Training Conferences, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    By Donald F. Lane. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Foremanship Training in Technical College, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Job Instructor Training, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Miscelaneous Papers: Job Instructor Training, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By U.S. War Manpower Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Automotive Company Practices with Respect to Foremen, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By Automotive Council for War Production. Study Number II Communication with the Foremen. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Foreman Training Courses Part I, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By U.S. Federal Board for Vocational Education. Bulletin No. 36. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Foreman Training Courses Part II, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Where do Executives Come From?, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By Chevrolet Motor Co. Forge Plant. Unbound, typed papers inside a large envelope. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Proceedings of the Third Annual National Conference of Educational Directors in Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Foremen. Occurred March 6-8, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Proceedings of the First Annual National Conference of Educational Directors in Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Foremen. March 17-18, 1944. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Foreman Organization, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Gerard D. Reilly. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Statement of the Position by the Foreman's Association of America in Respect to Pending Labor Legislation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Carl Brown. Correspondence to the United States Senate Labor and Public Welfare Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Should Foremen Join Labor Unions?, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Leo Wolman; Robert H. Keys; Hamilton Eames. Transcription of radio broadcast "Wake Up America!"; Broadcast No. 316; April 23, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Packard Motor Car Company (Petitioner) vs National Labor Relations Board (Respondent): Petition for Writ of Certiorari, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Supreme Court. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Brief of Packard Motor Car Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By U.S. National Labor Relations Board. Case No. 7-R-1884; in the matter of Packard Motor Car Company and Foreman's Association of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: National Labor Relations Board (Petitioner) vs. Packard Motor Car Company (Respondent): Brief for Respondent, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Court of Appeals: Sixth Circuit. On Petition for Enforcement of an order of the National Labor Relations Board; No. 10, 157. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: National Labor Relations Board (Petitioner) vs. Packard Motor Car Company (Respondent): Petition of Respondent for Rehearsing and Brief in Support Thereof, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Court of Appeals: Sixth Circuit. No. 10,157. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Packard Motor Car Company (Petitioner) vs National Labor Relations Board (Respondent): Brief for Petitioner, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Unionization of Management, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By H. W. Anderson. Talk given before General Motors Club of Indianapolis on June 6, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Union Membership and Collective Bargaining by Foremen, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Florence Peterson. Memorandum No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Union Membership and Collective Bargaining by Foremen, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Florence Peterson. Memorandum No. 7; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Unionization of Foremen and Supervisors, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Amy R. Jennings. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Problems of the Foreman and His Place in the B. F. Goodrich Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By T. G. Graham. Talk given on April 21, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Testimony of T. G. Graham at Hearing on The Unionization of Management, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By T. G. Graham. July 24, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Union Membership and Collective Bargaining by Foremen, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Bulletin No. 745. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Supervisory Employees: A New Problem in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By Research Institute of America. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Committee on Human Relations in Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    By W. Lloyd Warner. Reprinted from Applied Anthropology Vol. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Report on Foremanship Attitudes, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    By National Foremen's Institute, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Place of the Industrial Foreman in the American Economic System, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    By H. M. Taliaferro. Address to the Senate on February 14, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Foreman's Guide to Labor Relations, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Bulletin No. 66. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Foreman's Prayer, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    No author or year given. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Foreman: Master and Victim of Double Talk, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    By Fritz J. Roethlisberger. Reprinted from the Harvard Business Review, XXIII. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Your Supervisory Job in Wartime, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    By Glenn Gardiner. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: What a Supervisor Should Know about Himself, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By Charles R. Hook. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Foreman's Place in Management, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By Myron Clark. Research Bulletin No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Foreman Views His Place In Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By Foremanship Foundation. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Foreman as a Member of Management, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The Foreman in Small Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By Philip E. Henderson. Small Business Management Series No. 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Our Foremen and Our Freedom, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By William L. McGrath. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: How to Rate Yourself, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By BNA, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Constitution of the Foreman's Association of America and Laws Governing Chapters, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By Foreman's Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The National Foremen's Institute: What It Is and How It Works, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By National Foremen's Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What It Is, How It Works, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Essential Facts on the British Foreman, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    By Anthony Hamblin; Keith Thurley; Dolores Voon. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Supervisor of the '70s, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    By Robert D. Gray. Address presented at 1970 Management Conference on March 10, 1970; Lecture number 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Foreman: Most Mis-used, Accuesed and Abused Man in Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    By John A. Patton. Address before the National Machine Tool Builder's Association on October 11, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Graduate Foremen in Manufacturing and Similar U.S. Organization, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    By Kenneth Hopper. Research report. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labour Conditions in War Contracts, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    By International Labour Office. Studies and Reports Series D (Wages and Hours of Work) No. 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labour Conditions in War Contracts, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    By International Labour Office. Second Edition; Studies and Reports Series D (Wages and hours of Work) No. 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Wage Rate Laws on Public works, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    By John M. Carmody; E. W. Clark. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: White Paper: Rights of Public Service Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    By Canadian Union of Public Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Perspective in Public Employee Negotiation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    By Keith Ocheltree. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Organized Public Employee Relations: An Annotated Bibliography of Periodical Literature, Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    By Belmont Brice, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Relations in Public Employment, Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    By University of California Berkeley, Institute of Industrial Relations. Proceedings of the second annual conference on the problems and opportunities of public employees in their relations with public insitutions as employers; February 7, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Relations in Public Employment, Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    By University of California Berkeley, Institute of Industrial Relations. Proceedings of a conference on the problems and opportunities of public employees in their relations with public insitutions as employers; April 19, 1958. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Negotiating for Productivity in Sanitation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    By George W. Brooks. Strengthening Local Government Through Better Labor Relations No. 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Change: The Impact of Unions on Local Government, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    By David T. Stanley. Strengthening Local Government Through Better Labor Relations No. 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Third National Survey of Employee Benefits for Full-Time Personnel of U.S. Municipalities, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    By Edward H. Friend; Albert Pike. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Second National Survey of Employee Benefits for Full-Time Personnel of U.S. Municipalities, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    By Edward H. Friend. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: First National Survey of Employee Benefits for Full-Time Personnel of U.S. Municipalities, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Fourth National Survey of Employee Benefits for Full-Time Personnel of U.S. Municipalities, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    By Edward H. Friend; David F. Bencivenga. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Municipal Revenues: Bits and Pieces, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    By Wristow W. Crouch. Strengthening Local Government Through Better Labor Relations No. 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The City Prepares for Labor Relations: The Experience in Detroit, Baltimore and Milwaukee, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    By Al Leggat. Strengthening Local Government Through Better Labor Relations No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Municipal Negotiations: From Difference to Agreement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    By Allan W. Drachman. Strengthening Local Government Through Better Labor Relations No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Resources for Resolving Municipal Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    By Murray Seeger. Strengthening Local Government Through Better Labor Relations No. 2. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations, Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    By State of New York. Report of January 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations Final Report, Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    By State of New York. March 31, 1966. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Government's Place in Postwar Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
    By H. W. Prentis, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Road to Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
    By Carlton Koepge. Ten year study; 82nd Congress, 2d Session; House Document No. 563. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO Manual for Federal Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    By AFL-CIO. AFL-CIO Publication No. 138. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: PERC One Year Later, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    By Rutgers University, Institute of Management and Labor. Papers presented at a conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Employee - Management Relations in the Public Service: Supplement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Bibliography; No. 1, supplement no. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employee - Management Relations in The Public Service: Supplement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Bibliography; No. 1, Supplement No. 1. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Government Labor Relations in Transition, Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
    By Keith Ocheltree. Personnel report no. 662. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee - Management Relations in the Public Service, Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Bibliography no.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Organization and Collective Bargaining in Public Employment, Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
    By University of California Los Angeles, Institute of Industrial Relations. Selected papers presented at a two-day conference on employee relations in public agencies - February 1-2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor-Management Relations in Public Employment, Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
    By Michigan State University. Selected Bibliography. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Henry Laurence Gantt Memorial Gold Medal, Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
    By Jess H. Davis; Charles A. Jurgensen; Austin J. Tobin. Three addresses for medalist Austin J. Tobin. Item is in English.
- Box 9, Folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Better Federal Personnel Management, Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Unionization of Public Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    By William A. Korns. Editorial Research Reports Vol. II, No. 2; July 10, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Government Careers for Women: A Study of the Salaries and Positions of Women White-Collar Employees in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Needed: A Civilian Reserve, Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    By Helen Hill Miller. Planning Pamplhets No. 86. Item is in English.
- Box 10, Folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Right of Foremen to Organize for the Purpose of Collective Bargaining in Sweden, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)